<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mysql on I aM YUVII</title>
    <link>/tags/mysql/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mysql on I aM YUVII</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 13:56:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/mysql/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing LAMP stack on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>/posts/installing-lamp-stack-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/installing-lamp-stack-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>LAMP is short for Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP. This tutorial shows how you can install LAMP stack (Apache2, PHP and MySQL) on an Ubuntu 16.04 server.
Apache To install Apache you must install the Metapackage apache2. This can be done by searching for and installing in the Software Centre, or by running the following command.
sudo apt-get install apache2 MySQL To install MySQL you must install the Metapackage mysql-server. This can be done by searching for and installing in the Software Centre, or by running the following command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last flight to PHP7</title>
      <link>/posts/last-flight-php7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/last-flight-php7/</guid>
      <description>Eleven years after its 5.0 release, a new major version is finally coming our way!. PHP7 is out, and it’s time to get your code ready. I’ve already started migrating from 5.6 to 7, Here is the official document for Migration PHP 5.6 to 7.
But how will this impact your current PHP codebase? What really changed? How safe is it to update? This post will answer these questions and give you a taste of what’s to come with PHP7</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MySQL Import/Export large databases</title>
      <link>/posts/mysql-import-export-large-databases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mysql-import-export-large-databases/</guid>
      <description>When working with MySQL I often use tools like PhpMyAdmin or sequelPro, which is a nice GUI way to manipulate MySQL database. But it won’t work sometime while importing/exporting larger databases. So sometimes you need to do mysql import on the command line.
Export a Large Database $ mysqldump -u [USERNAME] -p [DBNAME] | gzip &amp;gt; [/path_to_file/DBNAME].sql.gz MySQL Import a Large Database # First, unzip the file. $ gzip -d [/path_to_file/DBNAME].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install PhpMyAdmin on centOS</title>
      <link>/posts/install-phpmyadmin-centos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/install-phpmyadmin-centos/</guid>
      <description>What is PhpMyAdmin? PhpMyAdmin is one of the most popular applications for MySQL databases management. It is a free tool written in PHP. Through this software you can create, alter, drop, delete, import and export MySQL database tables. You can run MySQL queries, optimize, repair and check tables, change collation and execute other database management commands. Install PhpMyAdmin isn’t an easy task. You need to do several configuration after installation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing GoDaddy SSL Certificate on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>/posts/installing-godaddy-ssl-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/installing-godaddy-ssl-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Basically in order to successfully install an SSL certificate you need the following things
 CSR file Private key Certificate key Certificate chain  Download Certificates If your website is hosted through GoDaddy (e.g. the primary domain on a GoDaddy shared hosting account, Website Builder), you don’t need to use these instructions; GoDaddy take care of the SSL installation for you.
 On your SSL certificate home page, click Download.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>