<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on I aM YUVII</title>
    <link>/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on I aM YUVII</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 12:21:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Google Map</title>
      <link>/portfolio/easy-google-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:35:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/easy-google-map/</guid>
      <description> A easy to use Google Map plugin for WordPress to display your business location on map. Here are the features list:
 Address marker based on inserted address ( i.e. New Delhi, India) 5 different colour schemas User can zoom it to any level User can set height and width  Screenshots </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Justified Gallery</title>
      <link>/portfolio/easy-justified-gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:35:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/easy-justified-gallery/</guid>
      <description>A common problem, for people who create sites, is to create an elegant image gallery that manages the various sizes of thumbnails. No Matter what size of images you have, Easy justified gallery will create a beautiful gallery using selected photos from media library. All you have to do is add [easyGallery] ShortCode. Here are some of the features:
 An advanced algorithm to justify your images without cropping them Ready for any device and screen resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram Post to shopable links</title>
      <link>/portfolio/instagram-posts-shopable-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:35:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/instagram-posts-shopable-links/</guid>
      <description>Through links.bio, seamlessly transform your Instagram feed into an engaging gallery of products, available to purchase with just a click or a WhatsApp message. Links Bio is a tracking system that cumulates information about your web presence and provides direct insights into your engagement, traffic and revenue gathered from your Instagram account. Features: Personalised Shopping Feed Predefined/ customised WhatsApp messages Instagram Analytics Multiple shopping links Advanced Analytics Coupons and advertisements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practutor</title>
      <link>/portfolio/practutor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:35:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/practutor/</guid>
      <description> PracTutor provides detailed insight into skill gaps for individual students and offers a scope of timely interventions. Its features help teachers and students pay attention to student growth more closely. Unlike a lot of online math/ELA platforms that promise to generate grade-specific excellence, we propose to bring in holistic math/ELA growth across the span of a student’s education. Technologies
Screenshots </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business management software</title>
      <link>/portfolio/business-management-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 12:35:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/business-management-software/</guid>
      <description>A modern and customisable business management software specifically built for MLM business models to increase footfalls and sales of your products. We also provide custom softwares to suit any kind of your business. Features: MLM Module with multiple commission calculator Module generator with customised attributes User manager with role base access Built in E-Commerce module Plugins like payment gateways, E-commerce, support etc. Technology &amp;amp; tools: Yii, MySQL, Bootstrap.
Features  Get all essential modules which are key to all businesses with customizable features under one roof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data scraping &amp; data warehousing tool</title>
      <link>/portfolio/data-scraping-warehousing-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 12:35:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/data-scraping-warehousing-tool/</guid>
      <description>A modern and customisable business management software specifically built for MLM business models to increase footfalls and sales of your products. We also provide custom softwares to suit any kind of your business. Features: MLM Module with multiple commission calculator Module generator with customised attributes User manager with role base access Built in E-Commerce module Plugins like payment gateways, E-commerce, support etc. Technology &amp;amp; tools: Yii, MySQL, Bootstrap.
Features  Get all essential modules which are key to all businesses with customizable features under one roof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency training portal</title>
      <link>/portfolio/cryptocurrency-training-portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 12:35:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/cryptocurrency-training-portal/</guid>
      <description>Take cryptocurrency guidance via seminar from experts. Search events with filters like date &amp;amp; location. Admin panel with role base access Event manager CMS Manager Booking manager Payment gateway.
Features  Get all essential modules which are key to all businesses with customizable features under one roof. Convert your product into an MLM enabler with multiple commission plans and structures. Build multiple stores or multiple different businesses with a single strongly built control panel Instead of using technology to automate processes, think about using technology to enhance human interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Theme &amp; Plugin development</title>
      <link>/portfolio/wordpress-theme-plugin-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2017 12:35:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/wordpress-theme-plugin-development/</guid>
      <description> Features  Custom Theme development Audio Plugin development Right click/Content copy check Multilingual Other usual features like slider, posts, pages, SEO enhancement  Screenshots </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile commerce solution</title>
      <link>/portfolio/mobile-commerece-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 12:35:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/mobile-commerece-solution/</guid>
      <description>Features  Generate ios and android App from Magento using custom developed connector Customize the mobile app theme from dashboard Generate and share ipa and apk over the air Enable disable modules like payment gateway, shipment type and cart like modules from dashboard. Send bulk sms to your customers using dashboard Send bulk emails to your customers using dashboard Other module like role managers, users management and a cms module.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>