<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Php on I aM YUVII</title>
    <link>/tags/php/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Php on I aM YUVII</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 13:56:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/php/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Execute Shell commands via PHP</title>
      <link>/posts/execute-shell-commands-via-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/execute-shell-commands-via-php/</guid>
      <description>Not everyone aware about PHP‘s capabilities of making SSH connections and executing remote commands, but it can be very handy. I’ve been using it a lot in PHP CLI applications that I run from cronjobs, but initially it was a pain to get it to work. The PHP manual on Secure Shell2 Functions is not very practical or methodical for that matter, so I would like to share my understandings on how to make setting this up in less time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get first job on Freelancer.com</title>
      <link>/posts/how-get-first-job-freelancer-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-get-first-job-freelancer-com/</guid>
      <description>Getting first job is difficult task for any newbie freelancer. After paying huge membership fees and bidding on 30-50 jobs they hardly get any response from client.
Actually 80% clients never give any chance to any newbie freelancer. So how you can get your first job?
Let analyse what are reasons behind
 Incomplete profile All talent marketplaces like freelancer , upwork etc insist to complete the profile , Profile information is necessary .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing LAMP stack on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>/posts/installing-lamp-stack-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/installing-lamp-stack-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>LAMP is short for Linux, Apache, MySQL, PHP. This tutorial shows how you can install LAMP stack (Apache2, PHP and MySQL) on an Ubuntu 16.04 server.
Apache To install Apache you must install the Metapackage apache2. This can be done by searching for and installing in the Software Centre, or by running the following command.
sudo apt-get install apache2 MySQL To install MySQL you must install the Metapackage mysql-server. This can be done by searching for and installing in the Software Centre, or by running the following command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Last flight to PHP7</title>
      <link>/posts/last-flight-php7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/last-flight-php7/</guid>
      <description>Eleven years after its 5.0 release, a new major version is finally coming our way!. PHP7 is out, and it’s time to get your code ready. I’ve already started migrating from 5.6 to 7, Here is the official document for Migration PHP 5.6 to 7.
But how will this impact your current PHP codebase? What really changed? How safe is it to update? This post will answer these questions and give you a taste of what’s to come with PHP7</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>