<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web on I aM YUVII</title>
    <link>/tags/web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web on I aM YUVII</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 13:56:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to get first job on Freelancer.com</title>
      <link>/posts/how-get-first-job-freelancer-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-get-first-job-freelancer-com/</guid>
      <description>Getting first job is difficult task for any newbie freelancer. After paying huge membership fees and bidding on 30-50 jobs they hardly get any response from client.
Actually 80% clients never give any chance to any newbie freelancer. So how you can get your first job?
Let analyse what are reasons behind
 Incomplete profile All talent marketplaces like freelancer , upwork etc insist to complete the profile , Profile information is necessary .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distribute your iPhone app over the air</title>
      <link>/posts/distribute-iphone-app-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/distribute-iphone-app-air/</guid>
      <description>Do you need to download and install an ipa directly from an URL? Is it possible? The answer is yes, to distribute your app over-the-air (OTA, this means without using TestFlight or the official App Store), you may need to create 3 different files, namely:
 your_App.ipa (The .ipa file using an ad-hoc provisioning profile) index.html manifest.plist  There are two ways of generating above mentioned files:
 Using Beta Builder (MacOS only) Manually  Using Beta Builder  Archive your build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a Freelancer This does not mean i will work for free</title>
      <link>/posts/freelancer-not-mean-will-work-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/freelancer-not-mean-will-work-free/</guid>
      <description>Yes I am a freelancer, Yes i work from home, Yes i work hard to make money but some people unnecessary ask for extra work , some people ask for free courses , some people ask for free stuffs.
I am a freelancer but this doesn’t mean i will work for free. I have bills just like you. I pay hefty rent , I pay for internet , I pay for themes .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things You need to know before hiring SEO agency</title>
      <link>/posts/hiring-seo-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hiring-seo-agency/</guid>
      <description>Working as Web Developer since 2010 I’ve had the opportunity to interact with thousands of clients and potential clients. As soon as website goes to production client keen to hiring SEO team and they seeking for your help. From the conversation with many of my client, I found out there are a long list of misconceptions when it comes to SEO.
Here are some of the common misunderstandings I see amongst my client when it comes to SEO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to start, stop and restart apache</title>
      <link>/posts/start-stop-restart-apache/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/start-stop-restart-apache/</guid>
      <description>Apache is primarily used to serve both static content and dynamic Web pages on the World Wide Web. Many web applications are designed expecting the environment and features that Apache provides.It can be started or restarted using any one of the following methods
Apache on MacOS Use following commands to start/stop/restart apache
$ sudo /usr/sbin/apachectl start $ sudo /usr/sbin/apachectl stop $ sudo /usr/sbin/apachectl restart On CentOS The httpd RPM installs the /etc/init.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>