<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ssh on I aM YUVII</title>
    <link>/tags/ssh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ssh on I aM YUVII</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 13:56:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/ssh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Execute Shell commands via PHP</title>
      <link>/posts/execute-shell-commands-via-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/execute-shell-commands-via-php/</guid>
      <description>Not everyone aware about PHP‘s capabilities of making SSH connections and executing remote commands, but it can be very handy. I’ve been using it a lot in PHP CLI applications that I run from cronjobs, but initially it was a pain to get it to work. The PHP manual on Secure Shell2 Functions is not very practical or methodical for that matter, so I would like to share my understandings on how to make setting this up in less time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website deployment using GIT</title>
      <link>/posts/website-deployment-using-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/website-deployment-using-git/</guid>
      <description>Once you’ve put in all the hard work of creating a website, you need to get it on the web so people can navigate to it and access its content. This process is called deployment. Deployment is a fancy word for “getting your website on the web,”. Website deployment isn’t a simple process, mainly because there are so many different ways to do it. In this article I don’t aim to document all possible methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSH Config to the rescue</title>
      <link>/posts/ssh-config-file-rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 13:56:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ssh-config-file-rescue/</guid>
      <description>How often do you need to logged into a remote server? that to using ssh credentials. In my case I have to log in and out dozens of servers daily. And if you’re like me, you have trouble remembering all of the various usernames, remote addresses and command line options for things like specifying a non-standard connection port or forwarding local ports to the remote machine. Hence, I thought to use SSH Config file.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>